John T. McCutcheon Papers
John T. McCutcheon Papers
- Published material
  - "So Lonesome for a Letter", undated; song inspired by McCutcheon cartoon; This item has been removed and sent to Rare Books. (Box 1)
South America B5F7 B6F6 B7F3
Soviet Union B2F7 B3F6 B6F3 B6F7 B7F6
Spain B1F5 B3F3 B3F6
sports B1F2 B1F5 B1F7 B2F3-B2F4 B3F1 B3F3-B3F4 B4F5 B6F1 B6F7 B7F6-B7F7
Stalin, Joseph B3F8-B3F11
steel industry B7F1 B7F5 B7F7
Stewart, Robert Wright B2F2
stock market B1F3 B2F2 B2F6-B2F7 B4F1 B5F7 B7F1 B7F4-B7F6
strikes B4F1 B4F5 B5F4-B5F5 B6F2 B6F5 B7F1-B7F2 B7F4 B7F7-B7F8
Supreme Court B7F5
Taft, William Howard B4F3 B4F5-B5F1 B5F3-B6F1 B6F4 B7F1 B7F3 B7F6-B7F7 B7F9
tariffs B2F1 B6F6 B7F5-B7F9
taxes B1F2-B1F3 B1F6-B2F2 B2F4 B2F6 B3F2 B3F4 B3F7 B3F9-B3F10 B5F6 B6F1-B6F5 B7F1 B7F3-B7F8
teachers B2F6
Teapot Dome Scandal B1F7-B1F8
Thompson, William Hale B5F1-B5F2
tourism B1F3 B2F4 B3F2
transportation B1F2 B1F5 B2F2 B7F5-B7F6 B7F8
Trotsky, Leon B7F1
Turkey B4F2 B6F3 B6F5 B7F2 B7F4-B7F5
U.S. dollar B2F7
U.S. Postal Service B1F6 B1F8 B7F6
unemployment B3F1 B4F3 B6F6 B7F1 B7F5 B7F8
universities B2F7
urban life B1F8
Treaty of Versailles B1F2-B1F3 B2F1 B2F4 B2F6-B2F7 B4F5 B6F1 B6F3-B6F4 B6F6 B7F6-B7F7
Villa, Pancho B5F1 B5F4
voting B1F5 B2F1 B6F5
war B1F2 B2F3 B3F4-B3F5 B6F2
weather B1F4 B1F8 B4F5 B6F3-B6F4 B7F5
Willkie, Wendell B3F10
Wilson, Woodrow B3F3 B3F8 B4F1 B4F3-B4F4 B5F1-B5F5 B5F7 B6F3 B6F6 B7F1 B7F4 B7F6-B7F8
Wisconsin B7F3
women B4F4
women's suffrage B1F4 B3F10 B5F3-B5F4 B7F6-B7F7 B7F9
World War I B1F2-B1F3 B2F5-B2F6 B3F1 B3F3 B3F6-B3F7 B3F10 B4F3-B4F4 B5F4 B5F6 B6F1 B6F4 B6F6-B7F1 B7F3-B7F4 B7F6-B7F8
World War II B3F5-B3F11
World's Fair B7F9
Yalta Conference B3F12
Yugoslavia B1F8
Zioncheck, Marion B3F3